Sex. Money. Power. How far will you go?
Web of Seduction is a thriller, drama, mystery film directed by Blain Brown.
In this erotic tale of suspense, seduction, and murder, a cleaning woman finds herself
working for two wives who are wealthy, idle, and ignored by their husbands.
The maid persuades the two woman to kill each other's spouses and live happily ever
after off the proceeds of their hubbies' valuable art collections.
However, the plan does not go as expected, and the
conspirators find that their own lives are in danger.
Simone, played by Lauren Hays.
Damon, played by Eric Acsell.
Jenni, played by Tracy Ryan.
Gerard, played by Franc Luz.
Stan, played by Michael A. George.
Brandy, played by Nancy O'Brien.
Dina Meyer (born December 22, 1968) is an American actress.
She began her career appearing in a recurring role on the Fox teen drama series Beverly Hills, 90210
(1993–94), before landing a leading role opposite Keanu Reeves in the 1995 film Johnny Mnemonic.
Meyer has acted in the films Dragonheart (1996), Starship Troopers (1997),
Bats (1999), D-Tox (2002), and Star Trek: Nemesis (2002).
She played Detective Allison Kerry in the Saw film franchise.
On television, Meyer starred as Barbara Gordon/Oracle/Batgirl in the short-lived series Birds of
Prey (2002–03) and was a regular on Secret Agent Man (2000) and Point Pleasant (2005).
She appeared as Kellie in the dystopian movie Amerigeddon in 2016.
The film explores themes of masturbation, lesbian sex,
threesome, softcore, exhibitionism.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.